the need from the customer drove their
decisions and so that's really going to
help the focus of today's conversation
um and with that
i'm going to hand it over to andy who
can do a much better job of introducing
himself than i have um but we're so
grateful to have you here and so excited
to learn from and with you tonight
thank you emma for the introduction
thank you for inviting me to speak it's
really a pleasure and honored to be here
among
kenya's tech community and fellow
colleagues from the insurance and
financial services sector
today i'll be sharing potential
ai digital ecosystem which helps users
become healthier
and wealthier and potential by the way
is 170 year old companies that's a bit
longer
so it's been around for a long time uh
firstly a bit more about myself i've
been working in a.i for uh well over 30
years now
and i i believe i'll probably be working
in aia before some of you were born is
that true
raise your hand if you're
i'm sure i think it might be true not
for me but for some others on this call
so for those who are in technology just
to give you a hint how oh i am for those
who are in technology do you know who is
alan turing
i'm sure you know
alan turing and zadiny hands
anybody want to write do you know give
it a try
no
alan turing of course is the father of
martin computing
he's also the father of ai
and um one of my graduate thesis
advisors professor donald mickey
actually and and alan turing uh if you
watch the movie uh the imitation game
how many you watch the imitation game
some of you probably yeah
emma watch that so you know that alan
turing
uh built a machine that broke the the
the secret code for
the german secret code and help the
british uh our or the ally win the world
war ii
my and one of my graduate thesis advisor
donald mcgee helped alan turing build
that machine so so that's that's that's
how i am
prior to working at potential um i was
working i joined potential roughly three
years ago uh so prior to working
potential i was a computer science uh
professor
for over 20 years
and my work at potential surrounds our
digital ecosystem
which is an all-in-one ai app we call it
pulse by potential
and you'll hear more about it in my talk
i also look after tele development and
creating a culture for innovation and
learning and potential
so before i
go into uh the three topics
of today which is customer centricity
which is very important to us the second
topic i want to cover is digital
transformation how and why potential
transform itself
from a traditional insurer to a modern
ecosystem platform player
and we see ourselves as a digital
disruptor
and lastly i want to share how we use ai
throughout the user journey in our
digital ecosystem
but before um i covered those topics let
me say a few more words about prudential
so uh i work in prudential's
headquarters which is now split between
london and hong kong
we have over 170 years of history and
among the top global for fortune 100
companies
now although the business started in uk
we de-merged the european operation
uh roughly two years ago
and we are literally emerging our u.s
business
right now this month
so moving forward we will be focused
just in asia and africa
because we see those market as really
high potential markets for us
so potential uh
we also have e-spring which is our asset
management arm
we work out of 15 it says 14 but it's uh
it's been outdated but we have four 15
markets in asia
eight in africa
and we basically have access to over
half of the world's population
with a market that is heavily under
insured and under repair under un
unprepared for retirement
so insurance penetration is less than
one percent
or only a few percent in some of the
countries that we work in so there's a
lot of
potential potential
potential is top free position in eight
of 12 light markets in asia
um
you may have also sure another company
called potential financial
which is based in u.s we are not related
to them in any way so we're not
affiliated with prudential in u.s so our
focus market is just
in asia
and africa
so before i talk about the digital
transformation of potential let me talk
about the the the structural the
business transformation and potential so
in 2015 we were basically four companies
uh prudential corp asia which focuses in
asia residential africa of course
looking after africa and we have the u.s
operation jackson national
and prudential uk and europe so the the
jackson and pedestrian uk
have been demerged or in the process of
being demerged so um
soon we will have this one company
and with a very sharp focus in asia and
and africa
in china we have access to 83 percent of
gdp
77 of the population of china
india we're doubling the 2019 ndp within
two three to four years
southeast asia were top free in seven of
the life markets including indonesia
and rapidly expanding positions in in
thailand
africa were top five in five markets
each spring our asset management arm is
the largest pan-asian retail asset
managers
with uh as under management of you know
close you know close to a quarter of a
trillion
u.s dollars
so who are we today
first of all our purpose our purpose is
really to help people get most out of
life
so that is that it's very you know the
purpose is already very uh very
customer-centric
we make and we do that by making
healthcare affordable and accessible and
we provide protect people's wealth and
grow the asset
and empower people to save for the goals
our customer base is 17 million
customers in asia and africa
and we have
products and solutions for basically
everyone
from emerging market mass effluent
high net worth and group customer
segments
as well
in 2020 we added 175 new products
into into our portfolio and that
includes health and protection insurance
savings investments
and then through pulse our digital
ecosystem we have value-added health
services
our distribution is multi-channel
includes roughly you know 600 000 agents
globally
and also 20 000
bank branches
through our bank partners
of course we have a distribution channel
through digitally through our pulse app
it says 24 million downloads but uh
as of today is way over 30 million
already
so we have very favorable long-term
structural growth drivers including
superior economic growth in the markets
that we work in
very favorable demographics you know
young
a middle-class
affluent as well
and then we're aligning with public
policy objective which is really focused
on
health
healthcare these days
and then of course we're transitioning
to a low-carbon
economy the esg is very important for us
when we do investments
in africa we work out of eight countries
all of them as you can see have
as you know
have very strong gdp growth
the
penetration rate for the insurance is uh
you know very low you know
less than you know only less than one
one percent uh in many of the other
countries so there's a lot of potential
um
some of the countries we are 100 old and
some are joint venture
in terms of distribution in africa
agency is 11 000. bank we have 600
branches so far digital is through pulse
our ecosystem in six markets
our ape has been pretty strong and
growing year by year we basically
started in africa only a few years ago
so we're doing pretty well
given that short period
in africa we have quite a lot of
momentum distribution this is uh this
slide is of uh this year uh the half
year result so this year just a half
year we're already 66 million ape and
that's uh 29 growth uh year to year
agency we have already uh increased a
number of agents as well as uh bank
concerns
uh
apa growth so that's a very strong
product wise we've been refreshing
cooper 19 cover
new products uh basically expanding our
range so that we have solutions
for all people at all stages of life
to help them of course make the most out
of life we're also expanding medical
offerings in uganda for example
in community we're also
giving back to community we have a lot
of education programs that we reach out
for example we have safe steps
which is a series of campaigns that
teaches road safety for children
we have cha ching which is a financial
literacy program again for for primary
schools
children across africa
and we also provide a thought leadership
on mental health at the workplace
technology of course we're using
pulse our digital ecosystem is deployed
in six
markets of the features which we'll get
into a bit more includes things like
communities where people could join
like-minded uh uh individuals for you
know to talk about maybe you know
fitness or or dieting or what not
we have fitness trackers uh there's
challenges to encourage you to exercise
but we also have challenges to encourage
you to say for example there's reward
wallets
there's uh digital products these are
bite-size products
which are entry level to get people you
know to get their their foot in the door
to to start um
protecting themselves or getting some
health healthcare services or doing some
investment
customer servicing is also done through
our app you could of course you know
look at your policies
do servicing of course and make claims
and then of course we have ai back
health information emi recorder
which i'll give the example later
and then
find hospitals clinics
as well as content surrounding health
well wellness and fitness
any questions so far i'd like to
like to make it interactive so feel free
to
feel free to ask any questions
raise your hand
says or just you know jump in and ask a
question if you if you like
okay
if not i'll continue
so uh before i continue with the with
the talk let me show you a video
um that summarizes our activity in
africa
[Music]
thank you
nigeria
my name is my name is mr chooksy goombah
my name is jim ogier chairman prudential
senate life
aluani to nigeria
balance israel
uganda
africa
africa is an important part of
prudential's growth story and we have
great ambitions for this continent
we want to become a leading pan-african
insurer to make healthcare more
accessible and affordable to the people
of africa
and to help them attain greater
financial security so they can get the
most out of life
[Music]
the insurance opportunity in africa
today reminds me of china two decades
ago when i was a ceo there
both markets have the scale to be
significant a rapidly growing working
age population
and rising middle class consumers who
are seeking to address their increasing
health and wealth needs
i believe there are three lessons in
particular that i learned from my china
experience that can be applied to the
business in africa
firstly it is important to identify and
to react early to opportunities
secondly to invest in building deep
local insights because each country in
africa is unique
and thirdly we must harness the strength
of the group so that we grow as africa
grows
[Music]
i'm incredibly excited about our
prospects for our business in africa
this optimism is reinforced by my recent
visit to the continent where i spent
more than a month meeting with our
employees financial consultants
partners and other stakeholders
i am confident the team is well
positioned to seize the opportunities
ahead
and to accelerate our growth building on
the strong foundation we have
established over the last seven years
critical to our continued success we
have the right partnerships and
relationships across the private and
public sectors we have deep seated
connections that have been forged over
the years and are hard to replicate
and crucially we have the right talent
to succeed
across our markets i met motivated
people who are driven to make a
difference to our business and to the
people of africa
our people are indeed key to our success
we will continue to develop our people
by strengthening their capabilities and
utilizing their talents
in africa we are currently in eight
nations
we have strong teams in all of our
markets ensuring we are close to our
customers and are able to establish an
early foothold in key growth areas
understanding the local culture is
important so that we can design
solutions and products to suit specific
customer
and let's now hear from our teams across
africa on their achievements so far in
each market and how we will be
positioning ourselves for even greater
growth in the future
[Music]
it has been just seven years since we
entered africa
in that time we have built a portfolio
of successful businesses across eight
countries
representing 30 percent of the africa
population today
since entering africa by acquiring
express life in ghana in 2014 we've
taken an adaptable approach to
geographic expansion we've acquired
existing businesses
entered into joint ventures and
established partnerships throughout the
continent such as our continued
collaboration with standard chartered
from asia to africa
so how do we ensure success we focus on
establishing strong local management we
implement strong governance structures
and risk management frameworks
and we share our best practice and
experiences from across the prudential
group both within africa and from asia
group beneficial a successful
40-year-old business merged with
prudential in 2019. the partnership has
delivered amazing benefits for me
individually as well as for the wider
team
we have seen growth across all areas of
operations working with prudential has
brought data driven decision making to
our intuitive approach based on strong
local knowledge
our staff have also benefited greatly
from the merger
there has been an increase in the
training and collaboration that has
given our colleagues access to a lot of
ideas but with the freedom to adapt them
to our local environment
this has meant that our strategy is
tailor-made and appropriate to the local
customer
i am astounded at the significant change
in our business in less than two years
all achieved without posting a huge
group of people within it demonstrating
prudential's ability to seamlessly share
its knowledge across new territories
we are contributing to our business
while also leading the industry
during covid we were the only company to
not just waive the pandemic exclusions
but also offer free covert cover to our
life and non-life customers
the impact prudential has had on our
business is a testament to the quality
of its people
depth of knowledge and the culture
within
together we are charting new paths
conquering new obstacles and are very
confident that we will be leaders within
the region as we expand further
i am proud to be part of the prudential
family
[Music]
clearly the strategy is working
prudential businesses have consistently
outgrown their market share versus the
rest of the industry
across all the eight countries
in ghana our agency force has undergone
a dramatic transformation going from a
sales to an agency model prudential now
has one of the largest and most
productive agency force in ghana
insurance industry
we decluttered our agency hierarchy
enhance our agency career development
and reinforce a shift towards quality
and this has resulted in a unique career
path for our agents
we also integrated our agency teams into
the wider potential family
this support system the world class
training they receive coupled with an
innovative suit of industry fest
products make fudensia a highly
attractive place for our agent's work
we made history in 2020 by achieving 19
mdrc qualifiers
this is the first of its kind in ghana
and this is a testament to the value
created by the prudential agency
[Music]
in nigeria
the seventh most populous country in the
world
and lagos economy in africa
prudential and zenith
have formed a strong
and successful collaboration
working together we have established a
hugely successful bank assurance
partnership
bringing local insights
and asian experiences together in just
two years
our bank assurance footprint has
expanded from 215 branches across texas
to 266 branches across the six states
in this time
premiums have increased 15 times
and policy counts are losing nine times
the partnership
with potential in nigeria has been
an experience
of tremendous optimism
and great excitement
the speed of transformation and the
quality of the franchise that is being
built
are
endorsements to how nigeria
and prudential
have worked together
as a team
and had created the strength of
partnership and reinforced the growth
expectation for the future
we feel very excited that the future
will be tremendous and great
in uganda our journey began five years
ago when we were virtually unknown in
this corner of the world
since then we have built the team that
is young
innovative and recruited on the basis of
their attitude and commitment to our
values
in almost all hiring our rule has been
no prior insurance experience is
necessary
today
we are viewed as one of the leading
places to work and our culture has
attracted talent from trendy startups
including africa's first unicorn
large telcos and leading banks
it is this team that has built the
company that is today among the most
well recognized brands in the country
with a vibrant social media presence
high employee engagement scores and one
which was recently voted the most
innovative life insurer in uganda by our
regulator
based on our successful launches in asia
we are in the process of rapidly rolling
out pulse in each of our african
countries pulse our digital health and
wellness ecosystem will accelerate our
shift to digitalization and further
allow us to connect with our customers
and our markets
it enables us to further collaborate
with our partners across africa and it
drives greater automation and
scalability it will broaden our growing
focus on health and wellness in a
significantly underserved set of
markets in kenya one of the most
digitally innovative of the african
countries we sponsor insurtech
initiatives to help ali and growth stage
in shorter companies strengthen their
product offering and drive financial
inclusion in the market
we drive the agenda to explore ways
insurance and technology can increase
people's awareness and protection
a key area of our growth agenda is to
give citizens the ability to participate
in health wealth and savings
opportunities
nothing shows our commitment to africa
more than our recent regional head
office relocation from london to nairobi
this is the start of an exciting next
chapter in prudential's journey in
africa as we look to reinforce and
expand our understanding of the variety
of needs across africa
and to strengthen our connection and
proximity to our customers across the
continent
we're building on our strong foundation
from which we can continue our expansion
as we look forward and think about
prudential's potential in africa
it's worth remembering the size and
attractiveness of the opportunity africa
presents
africa is a continent of opportunities
with a young increasingly tech-savvy
population and some of the world's
fastest growing economies credential is
bullish on africa and bullish on the
opportunity to serve a vast and growing
customer base across the continent
in addition to the significant
structural trends driving demand africa
is experiencing a digital leap froggy
a jump in the penetration and prevalence
of mobile communication has led to a
rapid rise in mobile money today 66
percent of registered mobile money
customers worldwide are in africa
and in some markets there are already
more mobile money accounts than
traditional bank accounts such as in
kenya uganda and cote d'ivoire
unfortunately the current quality of
healthcare remains inaccessible and
affordable for the most of the
population across africa out of pocket
spend is significant and almost double
that of asia this large protection gap
is driving a rising awareness and demand
for health and wellness solutions
at prudential our goal is to help people
get the most out of life by protecting
their health growing their wealth and
helping them live well for longer
nowhere else in the world is this more
relevant
through our increasingly digital and
ever expanding offerings quality of
product and service and resilience of
business we have a significant
opportunity to fulfill this purpose
the team has shown you great examples of
successes across the business and
highlighted the opportunities we see in
africa
demand for insurance solutions is
growing across the continent
to meet this demand we will continue
expanding our presence targeting markets
with high growth potential stable
economies and a conducive business
environment
as we continue to innovate and establish
quality relationships with our customers
distributors partners investors and
regulators we have a huge opportunity to
become a leading pan-african insurer to
spearhead digital innovation and to
accelerate financial inclusion in africa
[Music]
so
wow
so that's truly exciting time in africa
for for potential a lot of growth a lot
of activities
and what's really amazing is that we're
able to leapfrog with new technology
into africa
so i'm sure that pulse the digital
ecosystem that i'm talking about
will be a tremendous factor in the
growth
of the african business
questions so far
i see some of my colleagues are here as
well uh
when of course
so feel free to chime in in time as well
okay moving moving along so the three
topics i want to cover is uh is really
customer centricity
and then how that led to digital
transformation of course ai
uh customer centricity really starts
with our company uh purpose which is to
help people get the most out of life
this is first and foremost you know not
products not policies
and we do that by making healthcare
affordable and accessible
we do that by offering many fitness and
health features in pulse
our ai app
and it's totally free of charge for
anyone to use
you do not need to be our customers
secondly we offer bite-size digital
products to provide low-cost basic
coverage to as many people as possible
we also promote financial inclusion by
providing many advanced ai tools
available free to anyone with uh within
pulse to help people plan and manage
their savings
so we protect people's wealth
help them grow their assets
and empower them to save for the goals
you know our company purpose is totally
customer-centric
uh we also um we also see
and
why why are we building this this pulsar
making it free for everyone so we also
see that recent study by the world bank
and the world health organization shows
that more than half the world's
population does not have access to
essential health services
particularly in asia pacific region only
a few percent have health insurance
the figure is even lower in africa
many fall into poverty if there is a
major illness so we believe apps like
house
is a big step towards making health care
more accessible to meeting more people
and that's why we're giving it out for
free
the second point is that um
the world bank estimates that every two
seconds
imagine that every two seconds someone
aged 30
to 70 years old dies prematurely from
non-communicable diseases such as
cardiovascular disease chronic
respiratory disease diabetes or cancer
so that that's quite a lot a lot of
people affected so providing tools to
help customers take charge of their own
health
many of these premature deaths be
avoided through better dieting planning
for example or or regular exercising
so this is uh this is truly important
and at potential we believe we do uh do
well
sorry let me just get this eye up
so in producer we believe that we do
well
by doing good
we believe the best way to solve the
health and wealth challenges is to use
highly scalable ai
to provide valuable health or money
management advice to anyone who needs
them
we believe in giving back to communities
where we operate and helping the less
fortunate by providing affordable
and sometimes free
and easy access to quality health care
and money management tools
and services for all
via our
digital ecosystem
so for our customers
we see ourselves
more and more as a partner so for many
the insurance industry
just like us we're leveraging ai and
digital transformation to rethink the
traditional role of insurer
which has basically been the same for
the past hundreds of years if not
thousands
and which is basically you know focus on
just you know policies claims and
payments
so that's the traditional insurer
in the traditional role there's
practically no customer engagement
and the only customer interaction is
when there is a claim
now prudential has now moved to a role
that is more of a partner
in helping customers become healthier
and wealthier
customer engagement and reaction is
frequent and potentially daily if they
use our fitness tools
so it's you know kind of ironic in
traditional insurance you know
interaction ends after you you purchase
a policy
but in the new partner model interaction
starts you know after you you purchase a
policy
so we have uh and potential we have this
uh this model
[Music]
uh that shows how we evolve from insured
uh insurer to partner so it's a free
steps prevent postpone and protect
first is prevent preventing people from
getting sick in the first place so we do
that through a variety of tools such as
providing alerts for regions where
there's high risk of air pollution or
dengue fever
or copic cases
we also provide digital health
assessment
together with a digital twin which is a
3d model of your body to make sure
you're well you're well aware of your
body condition
we also have an ai symptom checker
basically an ai doctor so if you're
worried about
whether a symptom is serious or not you
know you use the ai doctor to check
second is postpone
you know postpone aging of
of or sickness through better fitness
and health
you know we provide a range of tools to
keep you healthy that includes you know
lifestyle
and wellness related tools
you know to stay fit with challenges and
communities to motivate you
so communities is very popular in in
many of the asian countries where you
know they're basically online groups
within posts
for people with similar interests you
know could be exercising could be you
know
cooking or or 40 group what not but the
thing is that you know with communities
you get to interact with other other
people and you learn from them and share
it also encourages your better habits so
we encourage
better dieting with things like meal
planning especially important for those
with diabetes
or potential for diabetes or heart
disease
we also have chronic disease management
to remind you to take medication
regularly and then last but not least is
protect you know if you do get sick we
provide easy access to physical doctors
and clinics or hospitals
as well as via your phone with teddy
medicine
and e-prescription delivery
so to serve our purpose of helping
people get
most out of life we have free strategic
objectives delivering we deliver
profitable growth
while making good social impact and
helping the communities we work in
digitizing you know we strive to make
everything digital from products
services and of course you know the
digital experience
finally is humanizing you know we
provide our colleagues with a friendly
environment for them to work
as well as grow and learn we also
humanize the experience of our customers
with odo you know online to offline
where human agents and financial
consultants can provide a real human
touch
so simply put our mission is is simple
to help customers become healthier and
wealthier so you can get more customers
interested in that and we do it all
throughout pulse app
let me just stop here just a second or
minute to see if there's any any
questions reaction from the audience
um
mine is just to sort of uh call out to
our cohort um right the mission actually
has the customer at the heart
of it and i think that's really exciting
um jihan i'd love to hear from you
uh thanks emma um
i just have one question really
around
in terms of like the target market um of
course in terms of reaching um you know
underserved markets and so on they might
not necessarily have access to you know
consistent um maybe use of an app and so
on so
for example in those kinds of cases you
know what sort of strides are being made
to sort of capture that market as well
yeah that's a good question um
before i answer that uh
would some of my uh african colleagues
be president who wants to chime in and
take that
if if not i think what we're doing right
now is uh first first of all we we have
this uh pulse platform
which runs on on um on android and ios
and we're in the process of rolling out
to uh you know all the countries and all
the functionalities uh
within that
for
the population that does not have access
to those sophisticated phones there's
there's many approaches
that's been adopted in uh by by other
people as well
is that there are for example there
there could be community centers where
they might have such a phone
and they and they access the services
through that through that location
or they have
they have communities
or groups or schools etc
i think
africa
uh is moving pretty very
fast in terms of technology adoption
and um i'm sure the
the percentage of the population that
will be
upgrading to newer phones you know it's
going to happen sooner or later
depending on the country
so we will see how how it goes uh i
think my first priority is really to
roll out everything that we have in
pulse first
um within the current platform to as
many people as possible
and then evaluate
at that stage a later stage when that's
done
the situation
in terms of
mobile adoption in africa to see our our
next strategy moving forward
so hopefully that doesn't really
completely answer your question but i
think what we're what i'm saying is that
we we're putting all the digital uh
technology we have from asia pacific to
africa first that's the first step and
then once that's done you know we'll see
we'll we'll evaluate the situation again
but uh there's also additional options
where you're not necessary to have
everyone to have a phone it could be
shared among communities groups you know
schools organizations and so forth and
they could still benefit from
from the ai doctor and health services
this is a great question so important
question
is one that we've been
following closely as well
any other question
okay if not let me continue with the
presentation
so um this slide is uh gives a bit more
detail about our pulse ecosystem so this
is part of our digitizing of our product
services and experience
so at the top
is you know you notice that delivering
roadmap in 21 months what that means is
that the app has has barely been
launched you know just 21 months ago ago
and currently we have over 30 million
downloads already
across across uh
the 17 countries that that's available
in
and the
source of customers that that download
our app
comes from first of all from our digital
marketing efforts in social media you
know facebook youtube and so forth
it also comes from our partners
and our partners ecosystem so pulse
itself is a digital ecosystem
that includes you know health wealth as
well as smes
but being a digital ecosystem what that
really means is that we have we have uh
a lot of digital partnerships that we
could tap into uh we all also embed it
in other people's uh digital ecosystem
as well and some of the partnership
includes you know a really large
retailers
uh banks uh payment gateways uh telco
companies et cetera et cetera so out of
that uh you know it says 24 but it's a
really so this this slide is in june of
this year just a few months ago but now
it's already over 30 million
downloads
up and down all those who downloaded we
have you know close to 10 10 million
registration
um in pubs itself we have 23 service
partnerships
we have accepted 86 communities
with of
377 000 people joining those communities
so it's very active
we have 1.6 million freemium cover
as well as 1.8 million health services
usage to prevent the pulse out
we have we have offering uh bite size by
size digital products so far it's 337
of those purchased
as well as some feed-based package
products where we package several things
together and maybe including
a subscription
so forth
from all these interactions in our pulse
ecosystem pulse app
we are able to
identify a high potential
customers as leads so we generated 2.7
million leads from the digital ecosystem
and that resulted in 174 000 uh you know
regular policy uh sold
um so that that accounts to uh you know
to 277 million apes or three million is
uh direct uh the dtc uh
sales
so it's very exciting uh it's growing
rapidly
and expanding so this chart shows you
some of the features within the pulse
app
it's not complete but just to give you
an idea
for example you know
our app is available in 11 languages so
there's dual language
biometric
facial login
there's a health check
and at the health jack you get a 3d
model of your body we call it a aido
twin
there's a symptom checker so if you
don't feel too well you could you know
use this chatbot to check if it's
serious
serious or not
and if it's something that um that you
need to see a doctor you can see a
doctor food telling medicine
which is of course you know very useful
during pandemic you know
and lockdown you don't want to go out
and fruitily medicine depending
excuse me depending on on the country
we may actually deliver your
prescription uh to your door uh through
delivery services like like grab
and this is great for those who uh who
cannot you know who cannot walk
conveniently
or the elderly
or people with you know chronic uh
illness where they just need to refill
their prescription there's no sense in
you know going out to see a doctor
that's you know to refill your
prescription so this uh telemedicine is
super convenient
uh we have things like you know a
hospital navigator let you know where
it's a nearby hospital
with the the the shortest your waiting
time for example
um
in some countries we have a
dengue alert to let you know which
region um it has a higher possibility of
dengue fever
there's selfie bmi take a picture
yourself for yourself you know we could
uh
predict your bmi using ai
gout buster to help you reduce
possibility of gout
we also have a chinese medicine
assessment as well
which is of course very popular in you
know taiwan hong kong
um
and then there's a health clinic health
content uh wellness goals communities i
talked about
i could link to your wearables and your
iot devices
vaccination schedule
rewards meal planner food journal
and of course you check your policies
and then we of course we have a
a shop where you buy stuff
and then of course uh employee flex uh
benefits
for uh for uh smes to join our group
group policies uh insurance
so that was the end of last year
and um and the policy ecosystem work
like that so first of all we engage the
user by becoming a trusted advisor um
helping individual achieve the
personalized health and wellness skills
and we do that through a whole set of
tools and capabilities you know ai
assessment
triage you know lifestyle management
heading medicine that i talked about
and then through that interaction we
identify
potential people who might need uh
whom i uh coverage
so that drives our revenue screen uh
we have you know d2c offering and
bite-sized uh
buy-side coverages we have customized uh
packages products third-party service
offerings
modular products with subscriptions
and then um
these d2c can turn to odo as leads for
our agents and financial consultants and
we could do virtual face-to-face
fulfillment so you don't actually see
you need to see the agents uh in person
you can
actually buy a policy virtually
using your webcam um
and and of course you know there's a
there's a lot of technology support for
that so there's you know e-document
document sharing e-signature e-payment
etc
uh
certain facilities in pulse is white
label so that we could also be embedded
into our customers ecosystem
and then of course you know uh
fruit pulse will also do fulfillment you
know claims and all the traditional
stuff
this is the status of the different of
capabilities and that was you know end
of last year currently uh there's a lot
more countries
so we have things like digital products
subscriptions virtual face-to-face
e-claims e-service e-wallets
e-payment
any question on post app so far
okay now
then let me show you a another video
that explains you know
uh
basically a summary of what i've been
talking about
um
how we put customers at the heart of
what we do
it also mentioned about how we are
digitizing our agency force as well
[Music]
in today's world customers are firmly in
the driver's seat when it comes to the
change agenda of a business
[Music]
they are the ones who make decisions on
product purchases and how they like to
be serviced putting customer at the
heart of the business is essential to
drive customer loyalty and profitable
growth
2020 reminded people of the yearning for
social interaction and human connection
is more important than ever before
with health and wellness as the priority
protecting from the unknown is now more
valuable
this means people are willing to forego
discretionary spending
for both health and life insurance
[Music]
we are always listening to the social
trends that shape consumers preferences
for insurance and health care
millennials are the empire generation
they are looking to grow wealth and to
protect their family's health
the silver generation is looking to be
healthier by preparing for fruitful
retirement
because we understand our customer
healthcare journey our health ecosystem
starts from prevent to postpone and
protect
[Music]
in order to drive financial inclusion
for all we have a world ecosystem for
wealth creation and protection
[Music]
these are delivered through pulse our
innovative digital platform to make our
customer healthier and wealthier
in 2020 we responded quickly to the kobe
19 crisis
providing relevant insurance coverage
across nine markets protecting over 1
million lives
[Music]
in 2021 we offer benefits for the side
effects from the covet 19 vaccine in
markets where the local government has
launched mass vaccination program
today these benefits are available in
five markets
under our we do well together commitment
we bring communities together
reimagining the way we do wellness in a
fun and playful way
[Music]
customers are getting both fitter and
smarter
they know their needs and seek advice to
help them decide
being customer first means understanding
them at a human level
nobody cares how much you know unless
you show them how much you care and that
you can be trusted
[Music]
we are trusted brand this trust is built
on the advice given to the 10 million
customers served by our agents we are
rapidly retuning and retooling our
agency force in response to the changing
customers behavior we have built an
active learning culture
our always-on pro-expert learning
platform has a growing library of over
1200 bite size video
this reinforcement of professionalism
and quality of care for customers has
doubled the number of million dollar
roundtable or mdrt qualifiers in 2020 to
[Music]
virtual connections has enabled
recruitment online
we attracted over 118 000 as parents to
join our agency force an increase of 13
over 2019
[Music]
to take professionalism over agency
force to the next level begins with our
agency leaders
our worst leaders programs redefine the
value proposition of successful
leadership
we are equipping our leaders with tools
to mentor agents for success to build
teams of financial influences of
tomorrow
to serve today's smart customers and
build sustainable business
[Music]
the first batch of birch leaders
delivered a double-digit growth in
recruitment active agents and
productivity this has given them
significant increase in their production
and income in 2020.
sourcing the right candidate is critical
in providing need-based advice for
customers
prove venture is our base camp for the
next generation leaders our profiling
assessment through dna helps select
those with propensity to succeed
provenge provides them with success
assurances through coaching learning
and intensive training we empower and
fast track them to become mdrts in earn
lead others to become mdrts
the role of an agent is to prospect
engage and advise customers we are
reinventing each facet of the role to
fit a digital business model their
traditional reliance on friends and
relatives is constrained by capacity
social media and digital platforms are
now a must for acquiring customers at
scale
proles at pals has a digital reservoir
capturing their pool of prospects and
customers
ai guides the agents for regular
engagement and conversations
now agent can offer timely service and
advice even without in-person meetings
this connection helped build lasting
relationships with our customers and
increased our agents productivity by 8
last year we are proud of our men from
the blue heritage with the iconic
briefcase serving customers from town to
town to serve today's digital citizens
our agents now carry true force and
powers a mobile first
all-in-one e-briefcase for all business
needs
we equip our agency force by integrating
physical and digital means to serve
customers our agents are the bionic men
and women from the food
[Music]
prudential is asia's first and largest
partnership distribution player the
region's most successful strategic
alliances of the standard chartered bank
scb and united overseas bank uob
these alliances underscore the value
prudential brings to its partners
our success in bank assurance is best
demonstrated by our 20 plus penetration
of the affluent segment where the banks
have the strongest relationship with
their customers
but enormous opportunities remain with
other segments including high net worth
mass and small to medium enterprise
which represent more than 10 million
customers
our health wellness and segment specific
propositions are helping banks expand
and deepen their consumer relationships
customers who want to access prudential
through their bank relationship expect
us to personalize their experience to
suit their needs by integrating
prudential and partner systems we
provide the best possible customer
experience increasing customer attention
and lowering leakages
prudential's impressive portfolio of
strategic partnerships gives us access
to an incremental client base
with the support of technology we've
adapted our strategy to meet the
proposition and solution delivery needs
of these customers
for the mass market who may not visit
branches we have developed bite-sized
digital solutions that address their
most pressing life and health needs
we were one of the first in singapore to
launch a fully digital cancer solution
through our partner uob
another example is a so far underserved
and significant small to medium
enterprise segment
our ecosystem of business at pulse helps
us expand our reach to these customers
with services for the business owners
data and analytics are fundamental to a
successful partnership
they allow us to develop models for
consumer acquisition retention and
cross-sell programs so that we deliver
the optimal insurance solution for the
most convenient channel
in 2020 we collaborated with scb in hong
kong to roll out a customized critical
illness offer with predictive
underwriting during the campaign over 2
000 scb customers took the offer with a
total sum assured of 200 million u.s
dollars
with increasing use of digital platforms
prudential and its partners are prepared
for the future of hybrid sales journeys
to help our partners adapt to these new
hybrid journeys crew expert provides a
curated on-demand library of insurance
content to equip our distributors to
better serve their customers
we've deployed our refreshed approach
across all distribution partnerships
both existing and new and it's already
delivering results this customer-centric
approach has recently won us new
partnerships including thai military
bank in thailand and c bank in vietnam
we are in the business of making
promises and keeping promises
giving customer what they look for is
our strategic weapon to sustain business
growth we are the leading insurer for
consumer loyalty and satisfaction
we are number one in the net promoter
scope across southeast asia
people expect prompt personalized
services at all times and at all touch
points
and we are making it easy for people to
purchase and own life and health
insurance
starting with the engagement with the
financial consultant who understand
their needs to a hassle-free journey
with real-time responses powered by
smart underwriting
our customer can get the coverage they
need seamlessly done over a cup of tea
customer no prudential will be there
when they need us most at the moment of
truth
this is a crucial moment during one of
their most emotional times
we promise to keep our word that all
valid claims will be paid as soon as
possible with compassion and care
our care extends beyond paying hospital
bills
we offer preventive health care and
rehabilitation program tailored to the
clients
[Music]
a claim system uses ai to make decisions
faster and easier and we saw up to 30
improvement in turnaround time and this
will go a long way to boost customer
loyalty
[Music]
while our customers are in the driver's
seat
we are guiding them where they go and
making the journey a pleasant one
[Music]
we embrace data and intelligence to
anticipate behaviors so that we can make
customer decisions with pace
customer experience is our new growth
engine
people can choose from digital cell
service to the luxury human touch
connection
our future ready platform embodies the
voice of the customer
happy customers stay loyal and make our
business more sustainable and more
profitable
[Music]
so
any question about
how we approach customer at the heart of
what we do
so there's a part of a big part of the
video is about how we
how we energize the agency force
with digital capabilities
which is of course a major change from
traditional insurers
um everything that our agents and
financial consultants need
are already in in the app
um it includes you know lead
distribution so they get leads from the
app
uh they get uh
they follow up uh and talk to customers
through the app
uh statuses as well uh they also uh
do learning through the apps
we guide them along the process
we remind them of customer
birthdays we remind them when policies
are due
et cetera et cetera we
give each agent dashboard to show them
how they're progressing towards their
ndrt
and then for agency leaders they get a
dashboard to see all the agents
under the organization
and so forth so the whole agency is is
totally digitized
uh with from from onboarding to learning
to from you know even from recruitment
uh all the way to mdrt
so that's that's well that's a major
change on the agency's side so we're not
only uh providing digital ecosystem for
our customers but also for our agency
force which is uh which is pretty
sizable
okay next i'll talk about very quickly
digital transformation i see we have
roughly an hour left so digital
transformation
and you know we're very fortunate you
know we start our digital transformation
journey roughly three or four years ago
way before the pandemic but many other
companies have struggled because they do
not have a well-formulated digital
strategy
so so the the the following sets of
slides talk about the digital
transformation in general as well as
some of the specific things that that we
do that we did
so you know needless to say covert 19
has changed all aspects of our life you
know how we work how we live you know
how how we get entertained and you know
how children get study so any company
without a digital presence
or without a good digital customer
experience are disappearing quickly and
you see many companies disappear over
the past
couple of years so with all of a lot of
activities going digital
you know digital having a strategy for
digital uh transformation is very
important
um a study shows that 45 percent of
customers
plan to continue to use more online
surfaces even at pandemic you know
whenever you know that would happen
uh so having a digital and digital
transformation strategy is super
important for companies
of all sizes and unfortunately we we
start on that journey a long time ago
one of the one things that we notice is
that you know cover 19 has really
accelerated digital transformation
some site by five or even seven years
so there's a sense of urgency uh to be
fully digital
and and for a company to undergo digital
transformation asap
now for the insurance industry this is
very evident and obviously you know um
the audience here know this very well
uh prior to copenhagen
due to type of products we offer and
various government regulations
practically most of our products could
not be sold
virtually it has to be sold face-to-face
i i don't know if that's a similar
situation in africa but at least in asia
it's uh in asia um region you know the
regulators want us to sell these
products face-to-face
to explain the products mainly
uh to make sure the customers understand
what they're buying so with copper 19
insurance regulators across asia quickly
established new policies and guidelines
for virtual selling
so
so currently over 90 of what we offer
could be sold virtually so this is a
major change from from from close to
zero to 90 percent
and this requires adoption of range of a
lot of new technology including ekyc and
ai facial recognition biometric login
conferencing yeah e-policy generation
e-signature e-payment e-claims etc etc
so fortunately for us most of the
technology we're already using different
uh and different processes we're able to
create quickly put together a complete
flow adopt you to the new norm very
quickly
so i think the only silver lining if
there's any behind the dark clouds of
copper 19 is that insurance regulator
around the world finally embracing
digital and virtual selling and really
accelerating
the pace of digital adoption in the
insurance industry
would you would you guys agree
and um
[Music]
any any comments on of any interview
from africa is that the case as well
a lot of accelerated growth
okay besides of the celery adoption of
digital transformation
ecosystem is also
is growing
so being digital is not enough consumers
want easy access to related products and
services
all in one spot
if you don't have an ecosystem you know
at least you need to tap into partners
ecosystem to get the customer so
according to mckenzie ecosystem will
account for 30 of global revenue by 2025
and mckenzie and also known that
insurance companies have the opportunity
to create new sources of revenue by
rethinking the traditional roles
in adopting an ecosystem mindset so you
know you know we have the foresight to
to to uh
to uh adopt a a digital ecosystem um uh
several years ago
and uh and and and basically you know um
that is that the pulse app that we have
so at potential we created the digital
ecosystem of complementary services and
products that cater to full range of
health and wealth needs as well as for
smes
and enterprise business
uh furthermore our pulse ecosystem was
designed with an open api
that allows us to easily tap into other
digital ecosystems operated by our
partners
such as you know retailers telcos and
and so forth
um
andy i just saw a question in the chat
from
uh malefica
who actually has two questions
okay you're welcome to unmute and ask um
but one of the questions was around
driving adoption and use of the app in
africa which i think is is really
interesting
um you know my experience has been
similar
in the market here here um that lower
income segments tend to prefer
more face-to-face
less digital um so how
was paul sort of combating that
um and then a little bit more about uh
localization of the app so are you able
to
you know translate to different
languages um or are you able to talk
about sort of different cuisines um but
malaika you know please feel free to add
to that question
yes definitely so
so although this is a one pulse
uh depending on the country that you you
you download and log into
the the interface you see is different
so we support
currently 11 languages including french
the content is localized of course um it
has to be localized because of obviously
your products are localized as well so
so content products subscriptions etc
talk about nutrition and you know of
course the cuisines uh all those are
local localized uh so that's that's uh
that's the problem so uh definitely
uh we cater to different uh habits and
needs of of of the countries so some of
the features that that i talked about or
i showed before are only available in
certain countries because uh it is
needed for example dengue fever uh it's
more important in countries like you
know like malaysia or indonesia and so
forth and then we have features like
traditional chinese medicine which is
you know
mostly popular in in hong kong and
taiwan so definitely the app is is is is
customized for
for different uh countries
but the platform itself is just one
platform
um and you think of it as different
modules that we put into the pulse app
that allows countries to mix and match
um the languages we support you know
likes and 11 languages so that's that's
not a problem
definitely you know being able to
support local culture and it's it's it's
very very important
okay maybe i'll continue
and then i think
yes
um i think the other sort of piece was
just around um how you're getting
um uptake of the use of the
app across the continent um i think the
question was around you know
there's feedback that you know some of
the users here are less likely to want
to use an app they don't they want to do
things face-to-face it's very relational
um so are there any tactics that
credential is following or that you know
of
um creative tech as we think about um
engaging with insurance or or your
health
yes i mean it's totally up to the
customer so for for some
younger generation if they want to go
fully digital will have some backsides
in your d2c products
but if a customer wants to talk to a
person um
we we
we
so the app is connected uh to to our
agency app so
if a customer wants to talk to a an
agent a person
goes through our lead distribution and
it assigns it to a particular person
based on some ai criteria for example
locality
or maybe gender age or product and so
forth so that we match the the best
agent
to the potential customer
and then you know they could start the
interaction either
you know through uh through your
messaging uh like whatsapp or you know
they could meet face-to-face or
virtually uh through our platform as
well so definitely the humanness is
still i mean the main thing for for the
pulse is really to help the customer but
how they want to be serviced
very often at end of day it would be
through our agency force
the digital products are are really
small by size product just you know just
do
for those uh those people who are young
they just want to
we want them to get into the
the habit of
getting some protection
and then once they want to
go into a regular product you know
definitely they they need to talk to an
agent or financial consultant
so we see the pulse app as as really
something to help the customers but also
as a lead generation
two as well
okay
does that answer the question
so next is you know we talk about
digital transformation and ecosystem and
so forth but you're having everything
that and then that that addresses this
slide addresses that the question just
now is it's hard to stay close to your
customer if everything's digital right
and then and that's where ai uh comes in
you're through the online touch points
and footprints ai and all the data that
we collect
helps you know helps us better
understand our customers
their demographic their personal
preferences their needs etc etc
so i think i think you know digital
transformation together with ai not only
allow companies to innovate and create
products and services better faster and
cheaper but also stay closer to to your
customers
because you know
once you're missing that that human
aspect you need ai and data to really
understand your customers better so
using ai
customer experience can be intense by
making the entire user journey totally
frictionless with ai and machine
learning automation
you have
personalization providing personalized
content personalized recommendation
that precisely pinpoint what the users
need and wants and it could afford
so
you know staying closer to your customer
and giving them an awesome customer
experience is is the ability to use ai
machine learning to give each and every
customer a unique experience you know no
not one size at all
in the previous video we talked about
the man from the proof
and once upon a time you know this is uh
um you know this is a uh iconic thing
for potential and your potential famous
for the men
from the pre-everyone recognizes you
know this
brand was recognized for for for this so
our financial consultants back in the
day so that's a long time ago
back in our days our financial
consultant would visit each and every
customers
you know once a week or sometimes once a
month to collect one penny for each
person covered
and absolutely that's a long time ago
but you know by by visiting them when
you're each each week or each month
they're like part of the family you know
they would you know they would just
go into the family
sit and and drink tea chat with the the
family members get to know all of them
get to know the neighbors so they became
trusted advisors
so back in the days we had a lot of
interaction about customers
and lots of opportunities to upsell and
cross-sell
so in the digital world we seem to lose
that ability so what do we do
now in order to know your customers like
the the good old days the man from the
pro or more appropriate nowadays the
person from peru from the proof we need
data you know we need data so that we
understand our customers who they are
are they male female do they have a
family
what are their interests do they like to
exercise they like to run
but traditional insurers do not have
that kind of data
we have a lot of data but there are
transactional data on
policies
claims
like that
so we need to have something else so
that's why you know one of the reasons
why we create a digital ecosystem is
that we could understand our customers
better we could collect customer data
understand their needs interests what
life stage they are at
their financial profile
so that we can match the best content
services a product to fit their needs
and budget
at the same time we're also digitizing
our agency force you know you saw the
video
we have tools
from prove dna through expert proof
force
that basically you know end to end in
your digital for for our agency from
improvement learning
uh leads management
and so forth
so using for example dna we
recruited over a hundred thousand new
agents uh
last year
out of that thirteen thousand two
hundred or mdrt qualifiers so that's
pretty amazing
we have over a thousand bite size video
deals to teach agents everything about
the business
we also generate a lot of leads from
pouts
and fed that to our uh
agency force for them to follow up
so that's that's the digital
transformation journey and why we're
doing it and benefits
next i want to share very quickly
because we have a lot of innovators here
so we'll just share very quickly on ai
aspect
what are we doing in the ai
before i go into a ai any any other
questions about the digital
transformation
okay
so let's see how much time we have okay
so uh
oh there's a question i see
elias
elias you have a question
yes
can you hear me
yes i can hear you yeah this is amazing
and um quite enlightening and um
my question is just around
the regulatory uh maybe constant that
you might have faced because i know
pulse is working in a number of
jurisdictions are there
typical challenges or
obstacles that you guys faced in to
bring this out in
other jurisdictions
or
did you kind of engage the regulator in
any stage
maybe
if you can share something on that
yes definitely the regulators are very
important partners
we did we definitely got them involved
very very very early on
uh i i i i guess it was a bit more
difficult uh um uh maybe uh uh
one or two years ago when it was uh it
was new but
with posts in so many countries
and being a more mature platform a lot
of functionalities
i think most regulators and you'll
understand
and really uh welcome the innovation
that we're bringing into the insurance
industry as well as a health
protection
so it's i think the key thing is to be
uh to get regulators involved early on
uh to to show demonstration of the
technology explain the benefit i think
you know regulators at end date they're
really you know their their their their
objective is really to protect the
consumer
so as long as they understand the
benefit that we're bringing to the
consumer
uh they're more than happy with you know
what we've been doing so far so
uh yes definitely you know get get
regulators involved
uh meet with them uh show demos um and
and and be very transparent
yeah just a follow-up on this um
how about data protection um given that
um
potential operates in
europe uh the gdapr uh regulations uh
and
maybe some insights on that were there
any uh obstacles based on the data
protection side
and and maybe how did you guys uh
transverse
uh across such regulations
well i mean we we don't transparency we
follow other regulations
um and the regulations differ from
country to country so we we tend to
follow the strictest you know gdpr for
example
uh but the things that we do is our or
is uh uh uh
it's all all based on i mean the
regulations there's uh uh are really to
protect the consumer interest
and which is good uh i mean it also
gives us a guideline on what what what
consumers are comfortable with
so we we follow all the regulations uh
the
in terms of data uh has to be with
consent of course you know with a
customer consent
uh
all pii is is protected so for example
uh when we have partners you know the
partners will not have pii on
individuals
uh they might get some sort of random
hash that they have no idea who that are
so so there's there's a lot of things in
technology that we need to do to protect
the id
of individuals when working with
partners and and other digital
ecosystems
but um
but it's you know it's uh it's is is
i mean there's a lot a lot of technical
uh detail to work out
but in a day you know the the regulators
and the requirements makes the product
an even better
more solid rigid product
um and and um and by us following the
strictest rule that
that's in the market uh such as the gdpr
we're able to quickly uh be deployed in
in many many markets uh across the
region
so obviously obviously you know um
all regulators uh have different
requirements and and they're really
stringent on data privacy so the fact
that we are deploying in 17 markets
around the world
with different regulatory regulations
kind of tell you that the supplication
that we have put into our
our data protection and and privacy uh
support for the app
maybe just the very last question which
region did it move the slowest working
with the regulators maybe if you might
share that and and maybe where did it
move uh
the quickest and maybe uh what can you
tell us that that regulator did
different from them
there are good people they're all fine
they they they have different challenges
each country so it's kind of hard to
compare
not like apples and oranges
super things
okay
in every question
if not i'll quickly move into uh the ai
part and and and how many of the
audience are really in your ai techies
have a background ai
i'm sure most of you are
being insured that you better use ai so
quickly so this is this gets a bit uh
slightly technical not that much
so ai is very important people say
data's in the oriole ai is the the new
electricity that we get from from from
data so to make data useful you need ai
ai
can be used throughout the customer
journey so ai makes the customer journey
frictionless and seamless so from you
know this is a typical customer journey
from awareness consideration purchase
service to efficacy
at each point there's a lot of ais just
to give you example in awareness we use
ai optimized digital marketing ai micro
segmentation ai personalized content in
terms of the ads for example
in consideration when they're doing
research and consideration we have hyper
personalized recommendations
ei lead management robo advisors
etc and when they're ready to buy we
have your ai predictive underwriting
dynamic pricing
ai upselling cross selling
and then your ai rpa for example to make
it frictionless
in servicing of course there's a lot of
ai chatbot for surfacing it's very
popular of course in the back end
there's rpa
automatic claim processing air fraud
detection is all standard in advocacy
we have ai personalized customer
engagement
personalized content
in terms of ai technology and pulse
there's a lot i'm just going to talk
about four knowledge graph machine
learning deep learning chat bots and
then big data
knowledge graph is a form of ai where we
put knowledge as a large network
and we use that in our ai
symptom checker
and basically our ai symptom checker is
is from babylon
and what it does is it takes uh
basically the entirety of human
knowledge on the medical domain
and the medical domain because it's uh
it's uh it's very structured a lot of
knowledge is already encoded uh into
various uh uh taxonomies and and
and so forth so this is a snomed ct
which a lot of companies use for for
example you know claim terminology so
this is a basically a representation of
uh
coronal virus or or sars severe acute
respiratory symptoms and shows a
relationship between diseases and
symptoms so i'm not going to go for this
diagram but what what we have is that we
have a giant
uh network of this sort you know
millions of nodes you know basically all
the popular diseases known to mankind
in in a uh in the ai system and then our
customers using pulse could to check the
symptoms against this gigantic
encyclopedia of medical knowledge so
this is a demo
of uh using uh alexa we of course we we
don't use alexa we use text but this is
the same thing but using alexa to make
it easier to uh to demonstrate and show
the how a person
talking to the ai doctor and how the ai
doctor in the background searches
through this encyclopedia to figure out
what are the potential illnesses this
person has and let me just show this
video very quickly it's only like two
minutes
pretty amazing huh
so um
so if the symptom checker recommends you
to see a doctor you could also see a
doctor throughout the telemedicine so
that synthetic that you just saw now you
know with all that sophisticated uh
knowledge graph in the background is
available uh free prefer to use uh in in
africa continent uh it's uh
we have also worked with babylon to
translate into different languages
um so it's i believe it's one of the
most sophisticated ai doctor around
because it embodies you know decades of
human knowledge
um from from the medical domain and it's
been vetted by you know you know
thousands of doctors around the world
so it's pretty sophisticated
and we also have besides the ai uh
symptom jacket we have a health check so
you go through the health check uh it
generates a 3d
anatomical view of your body to give you
a sense of how you're doing
uh we also uh and if you're sick if you
want to look at a fine hospital
using ai we know your locality we find
the hospital that's nearby as well as
maybe hospital with the with the
shortest uh shortest way for example uh
if you're in in a busy city like hong
kong
uh if you don't want to go to hospital
you want to see a doctor you know we can
find uh a network doctor for you
uh and if you need tele consultation uh
we have a platform where you could talk
to a doctor through your webcam
uh the same platform can be used for
other experts not just you know doctors
could be used for
for for uh for dietitians could be used
for you know uh trainers could be used
for
uh your psychologist et cetera et cetera
so we're making this platform we call it
pulse for experts so any kind of experts
and then for daily consultation uh if
you need a prescription you know that
could be sent to a delivery service like
rap and deliver it to your home
uh so that was you know the knowledge
grab and and other ai so we also use
deep learning
learning of course is the most popular
ai these days
and uh uh very often it's used for your
face recognition so we have a bmi selfie
so you take a selfie and it'll be so
popular you take a selfie
of yourself each day you'll be gonna
protect your bmi see if you're improving
with exercise and in some countries uh
if you're doing you're improving if your
bmi is improving you know we reward you
for example additional coverages or
reduced premiums if you exercise uh
regularly so that's a good incentive an
easy way to check we also have ai facial
analytics um
and and this requires videos so you know
with with
bandwidth getting cheaper and 5g
uh so far we see more and more selfie
videos and and picked out you know like
tick tock videos so if you take a short
video yourself you know ai deep learning
could extract key vital signs like blood
oxidation level respiratory rates your
heart even heartbeats so basically
instant health check by by just you know
analyzing video of a person
[Music]
deep learning can be used for a skin
check too so you take a picture of of a
part of your skin that you use to think
there might be a problem uh we could
check if there's a
skin condition you need to worry about
uh could be used for uh male diseases as
well
we also have an interesting and very
popular ai exercise body so basically
you know you put the camera itself as
you do exercise
and it you know it uh it acts like a
virtual coach so it detects if your
posture is correct or not give excites
advice it also counts push-ups
so it's actually like your exercise
companion
um we use deep learning for ai oral
health uh
take a picture of your teeth if we check
if it's getting
getting wider for example we also have
gains help encourage children to do
to have good brushing habits
chat bots and rpa chatbots rv are very
popular these days so we use chatbot for
customer servicing so you need to change
ask questions about products for example
you need to change data about yourself
your personal data your address or
things like that so that's very easy so
you do it through this app
and and then your rpa makes actual
changes in the background for you
we talk about health a lot but we have a
full spectrum of similar uh technology
for wealth management so you could have
uh we have an ai uh doctor for for to
help you manage your your wealth
uh helps you do financial planning and
investment advice
and so forth
and then big data and machine learning
of course is most
important you know the main reason why
we have the digital ecosystem
is to get enough data so that we
understand our customers and use machine
learning to predict their needs so at
the end of day is really about you know
making the app uh you know as as
personal as as you can so
you know if you if an app offers the
same content the same product the same
service to everyone you're really not
not you're really addressing no one's
needs so ai and machine learning allows
us to understand our digital customers
much better
you know ai allows us to treat each
person as an individual a unique
individual
with unique goals
unique needs
and you know i i believe ai and and
personalization really adding the human
touch back to uh back to the digital
platform so that's uh
very important
and then you know
digital transformation dx plus ai what
do we get from that
you know we allows us to identify the
right person
and give them the right product service
or content
at the right time in their life and at
the right price and immediate right now
so totally frictionless and seamless
this is how
digital transformation plus ai gives
benefit to a company
i want to uh so everyone's very lucky
today because i'm going to share my
magic formula
with you and the magic formula is dx
plus ai equals awesome
cx which stands for customer experience
so feel free to reuse this but remember
to quote me andy sean if you do
so um
you know to achieve uh true customers
interesting you know we need to be
transformational
in how we approach everything how we
approach marketing how we approach
products how we approach pricing how do
we approach our online experience
and you know um
more and more i think we see that you
know ai machine learning
is is the key factor in providing this
seamless customer experience
giving people you know exactly what they
need when they need it
and at a price that they could uh could
really afford
so to end i would like to show you a
video which basically summarizes
uh everything that i've just been
talking about
so actually i could have just shown you
this video and then you know skip the
talk but yeah here's the video let me
show you the video that summarizes all
the technology behind
pause and why we did it
for some reason that is not playing with
sound on our end
i'm sorry
was there a comment
oh yeah can you check the sound when
you're playing for some reason i can't
hear but it might just be me
hmm
anyone else um
any other people here
i'm here
i'm sorry we can't
oh you can come here
yeah you can hear okay
so
can i cannot
i could reshare again just to make sure
let me just reshare again to make sure
yeah that'd be great
okay
here let's try try again
we have sound now
[Music]
my passion is growth
but growth by solving customer pain
points
so what is pulse
pulse is the world's first ecosystem
completely dedicated to getting our
customers healthier and wealthier
now why do we think of pulse
basically customer behavior customer
expectations are changing
customers now expect to use digital by
default
and this gives rise to a completely
different type of competition so we have
the traditional competitors
but we also have the new big tech
players
and we had to react
so when i first saw the pulse
i thought of this fundamentally in terms
of customer needs
and customer pain points
and then what we had to do
to differentiate ourselves in a
sustainable way
the way we understand customers need is
through their interactions with our
pulse app
inside the app we offer many useful and
sticky content
including digital health fitness
lifestyle and communities
the more users who use the app the
better we understand their interests and
the needs
with the help of ai and machine learning
we could build offers tailored to the
individual needs of each customer
those offers range from personalized
content
by size products which customers can
purchase directly from the app
to subscription packages where we bundle
our services with those offered by our
ecosystem partners
or traditional products which agents can
follow up with the customers offline
the whole user experience is simple
intuitive and personalized
so it gives us a growth engine so it's a
growth engine that can grow at scale
in terms of
customer numbers and yet still satisfy
individual customers
how does it do that how can we get
huge numbers of customers and yet
satisfy individuals
that's because we use data
data
data did i say data
and then we use ai to make sure that ai
looks after the customer first
and that we can do at scale
pulse has three key value drivers
firstly a one platform approach creates
enormous efficiencies from around the
group as we remove duplication and
centralize our considerable purchasing
and operating power
we have several hundred legacy systems
we are integrating and deduplicating
importantly the customer journey is
uninterrupted and is truly end-to-end
secondly
we increase the productivity of our
agents and banker partners the deeper
the insights we get into our customers
the better acquainted productive and
more connected everyone becomes
and finally we enrich customer
engagement insurance is a product that
is sold not bought
pulse is about engaging directly with
customers on topics of interest to them
rather than the interests of an
insurance company
these three value drivers moves us
closer to a platform business than a
traditional life company and allows us
the ability to scale volume at almost
zero marginal costs giving strong
operating leverage
[Music]
another key offering we've created with
pulse is an extraordinary sme platform
that is a catalyst for growth smes are a
market segment that remain hugely
underserved so we created business at
pulse
this is an all-inclusive platform for
business owners and their employees
providing hr information and benefits to
lifestyle programs
for smes in asia and africa business at
pulse is already helping thousands of
business owners help their employees
navigate their benefits and healthcare
as these employees further interact with
our platform and we create more products
to service them we help the smes
encourage their employees to develop
healthier and wealthier habits pulse has
also allowed us to open up new
distribution channels to further grow
sales we can now work with
non-traditional partners to provide
prudential services to their customers
in a purely digital format and there's
more opportunities to co-create new
digital products to a whole new set of
customers
[Music]
wealth service is another important
component of pulse
over the next 10 years the asset
management industry will face
exponential change through the growth of
china passive investing environment
social and governance initiatives as
well as disruptive technologies and
continuous margin compression
wealth services at pulse treats the
customer as a segment of one and
recommends solutions from a curated
marketplace of services
rewards products and providers all in
one space
and this will not be limited to
prudential products and e-spring funds
it will span a wide range of selected
banks other insurance companies and
asset managers
there's a substantial opportunity to
help solve the insurance savings
investment and retirement shortfall for
a newly wealthy population and pulse is
well positioned to address this
prudential is well known we have
reputable infrastructure deep experience
in asia and significant agent capability
expanding our reach and capability
through pulse for this new market
segment will drive significant assets
under administration and apa
pulse now allows us to address new
customer segments across the whole
spectrum
why because we make quality health care
and welfare accessible and affordable to
all
this allows us to create new customer
segments
but also serves existing customers
let me give an example by way of
distribution model now the distribution
model is simple because the digital
touch points now multiply the reasons
why our agents can then speak to our
customers
this allows us to first complete a
digital transaction and yet have the
agents provide advice and advice leads
to better outcomes for both sides so you
have the best of digital and the best of
humans
customers or their advisors can choose
subscriptions across the whole range of
health and wealth without friction
so what we're talking about here is 10x
10 times the growth both in terms of
interactions with customers but also
benefits
to the customer and benefits to us
for the customer
pause is a truly end-to-end seamless and
intuitive experience
customers can use the pulse app to look
up their policy information
submit claims anytime from anywhere and
monitor its status in real time
in some markets pause app enables fast
admission to hospitals within the
programmatical network
pulse provides potential with the true
omni-channel presence
supporting interaction with our
customers via any medium they choose
online offline or through our partners
technology such as ai and machine
learning together with data
have played an invaluable part in
developing pulse because customers have
entrusted us with their data we take
information security and data privacy
seriously to ensure peace of mind for
our customers
we have built strong internal
capabilities to constantly automate
and develop secure tool sets that can
rapidly monitor and respond to threats
in our environment in a scalable and
effective manner
the way our customers use pulse tells us
a lot about their interests needs and
how they want to engage with potential
using data in ai feedback loops and with
customer consent
pulse can personalize and provide the
most relevant content and products from
us or from our partners and we can
deliver it instantly
all in the support of helping customers
achieve their health and wealth goals
these technologies have also allowed us
to create engaging useful and often
entertaining tools for instance with the
help of ai we can provide a customer
with a exercise partner to keep him
company on a run or workout
our pulse ai doctor can answer initial
questions and recommend relevant real
world physicians
in hong kong we were quickly able to
roll out a covenanting vaccine full care
fund
and with our digital twin you can
generate a 3d anatomical view of your
own body
and receive insights and suggestions
tailored for you
let's look at pulsing action in
indonesia ruth a generation-wide k-pop
dance fanatic downloads posts to receive
exclusive updates on her favorite k-pop
band
as we track her activity we offer ruth a
14-day free trial for our buga plan
we see that roof is using pulse to
improve her fitness and track her
calories and that she's recommending
pulse back to her friends via whatsapp
meanwhile she hears that there's been a
dengue fever outbreak in her
neighborhood and remembers to use her
voucher to purchase protect care she
receives a nudge to take up the cashback
offer which connects her to an agent who
already through pulse has a lot of
insight into ruth's profile and
interests and is able to offer her a
more comprehensive health plan
meanwhile ada our 40-something mom
learns there is a sharia for all
community on pulse pulse ai sends nudges
to purchase protect care a simple
product with sharia value based on her
activity on the sharia community and her
age her agent helen receives a
notification from pulse leads and calls
adder for virtual face-to-face
follow-ups which leads ada to purchase
through chinta
at any time thousands of ai interactions
on this level are taking place to build
loyalty and provide us with more
insights about future communication this
ai driven digital marketing helps to
scale customer acquisition and provide
the best match of potential customers
with agents to shorten the lead to cash
cycle
[Music]
pulse is learning and automating tasks
that were previously human intensive
such as underwriting
servicing and claims
so that we're able to manage our
customers faster cheaper and better
here's an example of an end-to-end
customer health journey in indonesia the
journey begins when the potential
customer receives nudges on social media
and other channels to download and
register posts
once downloaded and through ai powered
messaging the user is encouraged to
actively engage with pulse
any interactions the user does such as
checking their 3d body or consulting
with an online doctor
these are fed real time to prove force
at pulse which then finds the right
product to recommend
this new lead is pushed to the agent
along with the potential customer's
profile and any useful conversations and
actions that have taken place
the agent can have a virtual
face-to-face all within the pulse app
and once the agent and customer have
agreed the right service pulse makes the
follow-through execution easy
more than 600 hospitals across indonesia
are hooked up to pulse for cashless
admission so the customer can register
for treatment and then submit e-claims
and track them all at a touch of a
button
if the agent wants to provide an added
value service and help with the e-claim
submission
pulse allows this to happen easily and
all the way through our customer data
security is our top priority including
one-time passwords and authorization
notices
our unique ability to leverage ai so
broadly throughout public's ecosystem is
a major differentiator
ai intelligence services benefit not
only our customers their families and
communities but also our ecosystem
partners distribution partners and sme
customers
so how do we make money
now we make money because pulse is a new
business model
admittedly you could argue the same
business model as other ecosystems that
work on platforms at scale
but not in our industry so number one
the business model gives us multiple
sources of revenue number two operating
leverage fast superior operating
language number three self-sustaining
growth
and number four
speed to market for innovation so we can
do things in hours not months
i think nobody's going to be in a better
position than us
in making our customers healthier and
wealthier
and because we'll measure this
in metrics that we call the health
wealth and social index
and there is a correlation between the
customer's health and wealth
and prudential's health and wealth we
will make our customers healthier and
wealthier at the same time as making
credential
healthier and wealthier
[Music]
okay
so let me just end with this one slide
to summarize what really drives us to do
what we do what drives us to be customer
centric what drives us to
do our digital transformation what
drives us to leverage all the ai machine
learning it's just one simple statement
we're trying to make our customers
healthier
and wealthier that's our very simple
highly focused mission
thank you everyone for listening
i'll be happy to answer any more
questions you might have
no questions too much to digest
i know we went through a lot of material
um
it sounds like there's definitely some
asks to uh to get you know the resources
videos online
um it's part of our um
june investor day event so we have lot
more videos i only show uh three of them
there's a lot more i can give you the
link to that
later on
so so all the slides are also in our
investor
presentations as well so these are all
public slides that you can get from our
website
at least at least most of them
if if no other question thank you for
listening and i hope you all have a
very pleasant uh evening rest of the
evening
for myself it's midnight so i'm i'm
going straight to bed soon after this
um yeah and andy thank you so so much
for for being with us um
if your members of the cohort will get
the resources from today to share with
you
um
but i think you know you've really
helped to
bring to life uh prudential's
digitization journey the way that you
think about data and ai and how you put
the customer at the center of your
solution um and i think really sort of
provide some fodder for all of us to
think about the products we're providing
how we can use tech
more
thoughtfully to drive solutions um and
i'm sure it's it's encouraging others to
think about you know how to partner and
engage with the work that prudential is
already doing um so very excited we have
prudential as a partner
for the bema lab program i know that um
i'm sure this will encourage our team to
want to reach out um and engage in more
deeply with prudential as well um so so
andy we really really appreciate you
being here um
thank you so much for inviting me
absolutely
um and thanks everyone so much for being
here um if you do have questions you
didn't get answered or you want me to
follow up i can always reach back out to
andy um and if you're in the cohort
we'll dig more deeply into why customers
matter um although i think andy's
probably said it all uh on friday so
again thank you so much and everyone
have a great night
cheers bye bye everyone
bye everyone
bye bye thank you andy
hey
thank you all for being here i'm glad
you enjoyed and excited to chat in more
detail on friday
thank you emma
thanks everyone
goodbye
hello um
emma can we share with us the
contact person for
kenya
for who
the contact person who is at prudential
in kenya oh absolutely um let me reach
out to the prudential team i believe
i'll connect you with gwen
um but uh let me just touch base with
them and then i can do an introduction
does that work for for your team
that's fine that's actually this is
power and then also if you don't mind i
know jolly
if you don't mind ap as well
all right so
[Music]
jolly
sorry so power
um apa and prudential
yes
okay cool
all right so take notes my brain shuts
off
at like five
but absolutely i hope you enjoyed the
the session this evening
it was very engaging thank you
absolutely have a great night
oh hi
goomba from uh